You've got half a day to explore.
Be smart.
Keep a low profile.
Like you were never there.
You must not change the past.
Wait, what are you doing here?
For real, didn't you go overseas?
Don't attract any attention.
Hey, don't just run from us.
I don't understand.
He and Lu aren't supposed to be back yet.
Where'd he go?
Okay, are we crazy?
That was him, right?
Being extra weird.
Yeah, or you think we hallucinated it?
Maybe it's the heat.
You could've warned me she was walking by!
This is too strange.
Here, I'm gonna call him.
It's not my fault.
Some of the cameras are dead.
I can't see through them.
We'll work this out, I'm sure.
Oh, crap.
Where did Dodo go?
I don't see him either.
I can't help you now.
They've left the radius of my power.
Dodo!
We failed the job.
It didn't take too long to realize
Something has changed in the back of my mind
Your eyes
There ain't nowhere left to hide behind
Time no longer flew like it was
When the flash froze everything before
Without you
I don't know if I could take this road
And I'm about to lose my mind
Every minute that I die back in time
Every single existence rewinds
Some physical pain in this eye drive
All night
All the heartaches and the smiles never faded
I know you'll be by my side
When we make it
Come back from the times
Back in time
Die back in time
I'm sorry.
We tried the security footage, but it was a wash.
Thank you.
You didn't have to help.
I'm grateful.
I wanted to tell you before I used to stop by your shop,
when I was in college.
The day it happened, I saw your son with someone, but said nothing.
If only I'd stopped them or told you he'd be here.
I could have saved you from so much pain.
I'm so, so sorry.
I tried to put it behind me that when I saw you, I didn't even have the courage to say something.
Listen to me.
It's fine.
If I keep on searching, I know I'll find him.
What you just said shows me that I'm right.
You've given me hope.
More clues are out there somewhere.
So I'll keep looking for a decade or more.
I swear I won't stop.
One day I will find him.
You can do it, Triple Star Warriors!
Beat the bad guy!
As long as we have hope, we won't be defeated so easily!
I'm sure that Dodo is out there waiting for me, dreaming that his parents will bring him home.
Daddy… Mommy…
Now then, enough talk of regrets. I should keep searching for new clues.
Excuse me. If you don't mind, I want to help out.
Thanks. That'd be great. Sorry, I kind of forgot you were there for a second.
Oh dear, it looks like your presence is unremarkable.
Dad, you take that back, damn it!
By the way, do you happen to have any photos from around the time of the incident?
None the cops found helpful. Let me find them.
They aren't much, but there's something. Hold on.
Whoa. Are you using the same phone you had then?
Yes. Happily. I don't want to lose anything saved on it. In case I'm overlooking a clue.
When were these photos taken? Close to that day?
Not quite. I would've snapped these the week before.
We closed and had a nice day. Just the two of us.
After the store opened, we honestly didn't have time to take many pics.
Wait! Back up! What was that?
Huh? Not sure what you mean.
There! That one! Who took this?
Huh. Dodo must have taken this one. He loved taking pictures.
I couldn't bring myself to delete even the blurry ones. He might want them. One day.
You know, I think this was from that afternoon.
Nobody looks too suspicious.
This could be it!
You don't stand a chance, villain! The powers of justice will take you down!
Excellent! Let me borrow your phone.
Here, look. It might be the key.
Let's go.
Star of justice, bringing hope!
Star of courage, conquering fear!
Star of wisdom, serving knowledge!
Orange black milk tea, ice, light sugar.
It'll be done soon. Please be patient.
Nice.
Any moment now, Dodo will be taken from here.
I wasn't able to see the kidnapper's face, or how they grabbed him. So watch out.
Yeah, it's weird. There's a bunch of people around.
Who would nab someone in broad daylight with so many witnesses?
You need to be careful.
This is our last chance.
Whoever took this child will pay. Let's do this.
That's it!
Be a dear, and give your sweet old auntie the bar back.
Auntie?
Hm. Why does this smell so good?
Oh my god.
Drop it!
So that's how it went down.
No wonder we couldn't figure it out.
Keep focused.
Snap out of it!
Sweetie, follow me.
See? Your parents are too busy.
But I'm always more than happy to play with you. Come. We'll have fun at my house.
Hey, why is their kid leaving with someone?
Oh, didn't you hear? That's his aunt.
His parents are way too swamped here.
I'll have a better time with her, I bet.
What's wrong with me?
I feel dizzy.
I can't control my body.
But my vision is blurring.
You need to stay with me!
Oh, let's check out the shop.
The line isn't too long yet.
Hey, it's you!
Huh?
Hey, wait. What are you doing here?
Dodo!
Abby?
Sorry.
Sweetheart.
I know that we're late.
When Gigi's mom came to pick her up from school,
she said that you and mom forgot about me!
Hey, don't listen to her.
Look, for you. Daddy picked out a special toy.
You got the Star of Justice! Can I open it now?
Of course. I was late because I wanted to find you all three warriors.
So, son, you forgive your old man, don't you?
What are you saying, liar? We're late because you were haggling!
You idiot! We should've just paid full price!
Come on, don't be like that. He can hear you.
He…
Finally awake.
The trafficker drugged you. You've been out a while.
Listen up. You're going to be out of time before long.
Where am I?
I'm not sure. You were unconscious. I couldn't see anything.
How could such a horrible person sleep so soundly?
Don't sit there. Investigate.
The Red Sun Hostel?
I'm on it. Just a second.
There's not one around here, but I see about thirty other locations throughout the country.
This kidnapper already took you from the city and hid you.
In that case, how did she travel?
She would need her ID for public transportation, which means she probably still has it on her.
See if you can find a purse or wallet somewhere.
Oh no, no, no, no…
Mine's my father and my father.
It's grown for that sister!
I'm one of her parents, but…
And I'm doing the same.
And that's what she's treating me anyway…
I know what, why are we-
Oh, what…
That's it.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah, I didn't work for a assistir.
Jackpot!
Damn, it's tangled in some talisman.
She's the evil one, but she's afraid of ghosts.
Makes no sense.
Hurry, you don't have much time left.
Bingo.
Her name's Mei Pien.
Her ID number is 594810.
81-81-81-81-0.
Very close.
Whoa, those moves I learned from Master Suen are no joke!
I'm awesome!
Watch carefully, you two.
This is called sending you to heaven.
Right?
Right.
This move can be lethal.
Got that?
Only use it for emergencies and don't use it on people.
She's lucky I'm a child right now.
I could have killed her.
You little brat.
Most kids are too scared to fight back.
They just cry.
But you, you dare touch me?
I'm gonna cut off your legs.
Then I'll rip out your tongue.
You'll scream and spend the rest of your life in pain.
Huh!
Evil me, Pien.
You heartless waste!
I can't believe how deranged you are!
Even the gods won't tolerate you anymore.
They send me here to teach you a lesson!
Maniac kid, what are you talking about?
Listen here, old lady.
In three years you'll be brought to justice.
Take my advice.
Look after this kid.
Start doing good deeds so when the end arrives you can beg for mercy!
Otherwise after you die you'll spend an eternity burning in the depths of hell!
You're possessed.
Who are you?
I am your ancestor.
Father!
Please help me!
Our ancestors have sent me a warning!
Ancestry's have sent me a warning!
Liang, try to relax.
If you're nervous, your kid's sure to pick up on something like that.
I'm not nervous, just excited.
I've waited so long for this moment.
I'm still trying to figure out how you got the info on this human trafficker lady.
Don't leave me guessing, man. What's the secret?
I met lots of helpful people. I have them to thank.
This world still has good humans in it.
Honey, Dodo is finally returning.
You need to prepare yourself in case the Ax Shire doesn't recognize you after three years.
It's important that you take your time and try not to rush him.
Yes, I understand that. And I'm ready. We'll work through this.
Hey, there's the van!
Let us know that we have to hug you after two months later.
Well, it does, earlier.
Yes!
Doodo!
My son!
We're here! businessman!
You're here! You're safe!
Do you remember your daddy, Bodo?
I'm sorry. It took so long.
Wow! It's the heroes! Hi there!
Star of Courage! Conquering fear!
Star of Wisdom! Serving knowledge!
Star of Justice! Bringing hope!
We are the Triple Star Warriors!
I'm so sorry, Dodo.
I was trying to find these warriors for you.
That's why I was late.
Now, kid, do you think you can forgive your old man?
Daddy! Daddy!
Son! You're home!
Awesome! We did it!
Our job is done!
Dodo, it's you! Welcome back!
Our family is finally home again!
Please, sir. I swear to you, I haven't harmed a single person in the last three years. And him. I raised that boy as though he were my own flesh and blood. He got the best care I could afford. I've repented my past mistakes every day. I beg you.
Hey, Mei Pien! Stay on the right track! Your ancestors are watching!
I hear you, Spirit! Thank you!
Cut it out! Pretending to be crazy isn't going to result in a lighter sentence or a judge's mercy.
Chun Bin, take her inside and start interrogating.
My ancestors are speaking to me again!
So, your name is Chung Shaoshu, is that right? And the white-haired boy is Lu Guang. Which means, the girl is Chaoling. All the rumors online about a powerful old witch are just a cover story. You're the ones who have the ability to enter photographs, aren't you?
I have no idea what you're talking about. Then explain this to me. Are you kidding? Chun was just here a few days ago looking at this. Why are you bugging me about a cold case?
Stop there! What is it? This guy a suspect or something?
What I'm wondering is simple. Why do you show up in surveillance footage from the milk tea shop three years ago? Hey, relax. I'm just curious about how your power works. Take this envelope. It contains photos from a major case I've got.
I could use your help, if you don't mind. Hold on. You should ask me. I decide if we help.
If I can wait for my heart, the
Oh, oh, oh, oh.